https://donnayoung.org/privacy/privacy.htm

DonnaYoung.org    Members  Subscribe  Purchase Files
Login
DonnaYoung.org Printables and Resources
for Home, Home School, and Classrooms
Read about the two different subscriptions available for DonnaYoung.org
DonnaYoung.org uses as few cookies as possible
The "At DonnaYoung.org"
Customer's Payment Information
Donna Young uses PayPal. When you make a purchase at donnayoung.org, PayPal will request payment information. Donna Young does not see, does not have access to, and does not store any payment information provided by you to purchase a site-cd, a subscription, or a download. For more information about PayPal's privacy policy go to: PayPal's Privacy Document.
back to donnayoung.org
How DonnaYoung.org uses Cookies
If you do not know what a cookie is, you can go here to read about cookies -- http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/.
Cookies
The Cookie Notification that you might have clicked on sets a cookie for the purpose of remembering that you clicked on it. This cookie prevents the notification from appearing again for as long as the cookie remains on your computer.
Cookies: Subscriptions
Members with an Active Subscription: DonnaYoung.org offers various subscriptions
and
when a member logs on,
a cookie is required. The subscription software will record the occurrence of logging on, the ip address used, and if an error occurred.
back to donnayoung.org
Cookies set by 3rd Parties while Visiting DonnaYoung.org
Please realize that opting out of these cookies does not remove the advertisements.
Please understand that opting out sets a cookie on the computer used when you take this action. If you use other devices to browse the internet, you will have to opt out on each device.
Donna Young cannot opt out of 3rd party cookies for you; you must do this yourself. The links are provided below.
Google Adsense
Donnayoung.org NO LONGER uses Google Adsense.
Google Analytics
Donnayoung.org NO LONGER uses Google Analytics.
Amazon.com
Phasing out of amazon.com usage.
Amazon's affiliate advertising program: DonnaYoung.org is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com or endless.com. You can read Amazon's privacy policy here.
Broadly Opting Out
Although you may feel safe browsing this website (because I have eliminated 3rd party elements), I highly recommend that you opt. It is your choice. Please also read the *Note.
You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.
*Note: If you regularly delete cookies, opting out will be a chore because opting out sets a cookie.
DonnaYoung.org Uses as Few Cookies as Possible
As stated above, cookies that might or might not be set when you are at my website are from these things and please realize that each of these
items might set more than one cookie.
Member's log in
Cookie Notification click through
Amazon (phasing out of this)
As Few Cookies as Possible
DonnaYoung.org does NOT implement social sharing scripts, many of which track you and benefit
neither you nor me.
DonnaYoung.org does NOT implement any type of FaceBook, Twitter, or Pinterest widget. If I do link to my social connections they will be plain links requiring no scripts.
The "at DonnaYoung.org" Links
The links at donnayoung.org that have a header worded something like "at DonnaYoung.org" or "Related at DonnaYoung.org" are links to somewhere on this website (donnayoung.org). Not all of the DonnaYoung.org links will have the "at DonnaYoung.org" header. DonnaYoung.org is a big web site and Donna Young hopes that the "at DonnaYoung.org" links are useful.
These links are simple links, meaning they do not track nor do they set cookies. They are laboriously provided for your benefit.
Links to Other Web sites, Off Site Links
Donnayoung.org
rarely contains links to other web sites of interest. Links are live and true on the day that they are linked, however; links can become broken
and they can point to content that is different from the original content. Donna Young is not informed when others change their websites.
Once you use an off-site link and
leave donnayoung.org, you should
note that Donna Young does not have any control over that other web site.
Therefore, Donna Young cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of
any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such
sites that are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise
caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the web site in
question.
Unusual or Unexpected Advertising
Donna Young runs a clean website and no longer uses 3rd party ads. If you see
adult-only ads or experience pop-up or pop-under ads on this website please check your computer for malware or adware.
Disclosure on Book Reviews
If Donna Young reviews a book, that means she has bought the book, used the book, and has an opinion.
Donna Young has not reviewed every home school book that she has used.
Donna Young might link the reviewed book with an "affiliated link" if such a link is available; otherwise, a plain link will be used or no link.
Donna Young does not review books by request.
Thanks for reading!
This file was updated Updated January 25, 2019 by Donna Young.
back to donnayoung.org
Subscribe for File Access
Subscribe to DonnaYoung.org or YoungMinds, and receive access to files and no 3rd party advertising, which means a faster and better website.
Color Study Printables and Color WheelsTwo new color wheels! A printable file named Boxes! Go and compare colors with these printable files now! or soon.
Copyright © 1999 - 2020 Donna Young, All Rights Reserved
RSS Feed
·
Terms of Use
·
Privacy Policy ·
FAQ's ·
Blog ·
